<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ABLRML12]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006122]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A M-LOK RAIL 12 W/ TITANIUM BBL NUT]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The 2A Armament BL RAIL M-LOK series was designed as a lightweight rail solution utilizing proven traditional 6061 extrusion and titanium as the foundation. The BL RAIL series of rails features the same lightening cuts found on the popular BALIOS-lite receiver sets. When the two are combined a seamless look is achieved across the top of the firearm. The BL RAIL is just as capable on any quality forged or billet upper receiver offered from other manufacturers as well. By utilizing a titanium barrel nut and an innovative 45 degree mounting system the BL RAIL achieves a solid lockup with the upper receiver. The 2A Armament BL RAIL will ship with a 6AL-4V titanium barrel nut. An optional aluminum barrel nut is offered as a separate item for those looking to save maximum weight on a build. - Made from U.S.A. Certified 6061 Extrusion - U.S.A. Certified 6AL-4V Titanium barrel nut as standard - M-LOK mounting solution - Mil-Spec hardcoat black anodized - Free floating design - 1.3 Internal Diameter - 15 Rail with Titanium nut and hardware (weight 9.60oz)(2A-BLRML-15) - 1-5/16 crows foot tool or premium armorers wrench recommended for installation (Not Included)]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[159]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[216]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[227]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ABLRML15]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006115]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A M-LOK RAIL 15 W/ TITANIUM BBL NUT]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The 2A Armament BL RAIL M-LOK series was designed as a lightweight rail solution utilizing proven traditional 6061 extrusion and titanium as the foundation. The BL RAIL series of rails features the same lightening cuts found on the popular BALIOS-lite receiver sets. When the two are combined a seamless look is achieved across the top of the firearm. The BL RAIL is just as capable on any quality forged or billet upper receiver offered from other manufacturers as well. By utilizing a titanium barrel nut and an innovative 45 degree mounting system the BL RAIL achieves a solid lockup with the upper receiver. The 2A Armament BL RAIL will ship with a 6AL-4V titanium barrel nut. An optional aluminum barrel nut is offered as a separate item for those looking to save maximum weight on a build. - Made from U.S.A. Certified 6061 Extrusion - U.S.A. Certified 6AL-4V Titanium barrel nut as standard - M-LOK mounting solution - Mil-Spec hardcoat black anodized - Free floating design - 1.3 Internal Diameter - 15 Rail with Titanium nut and hardware (weight 9.60oz)(2A-BLRML-15) - 1-5/16 crows foot tool or premium armorers wrench recommended for installation (Not Included)]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[185]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[264]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ACOMPT3]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006061]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A COMPENSATOR T3 5.56 BLK OXIDE]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[53]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[75]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ACU3008ML7BLK1]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006337]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A UPPER 300BLK 8 M-LOK]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The 8 .300BLK complete upper receiver offers the end user an assembled system that is ready for lightweight needs. Each assembled upper starts with a BALIOS-lite stripper upper receiver. We then add our titanium gas block on the appropriate length barrel and finish the assembly with our 7 BL-RAIL and titanium barrel nut. These uppers are perfect for those who are looking to do a suppressed .300BLK build. Our full mass carrier is included as well as a BCM-Mod4 charging handle. - Barrel Material: 4150 Chrome Moly Vanadium - Twist Rate: 1:7 inches - Finish: QPQ Nitride - Muzzle 5/8 x 24 thread - Carrier: Full mass QPQ Nitride body and gas key Stainless tail - Bolt: 9310 QPQ Nitride body and extractor Cryo'd MP tested - 7075 enhanced charging handle BCM-Mod - Total Weight: (2LBS 10.5oz M-LOK) (2LBS 10.7oz KeyMod) - Does not include a muzzle device]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H631]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[BARRELS]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[1010]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[1169]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[1299]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ACU556105ML10BLK1]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006306]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A UPPER 5.56 10.5 M-LOK]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The BALIOS-lite 10.5 5.56mm NATO complete upper receiver offers the end user an assembled system that is ready for lightweight needs. Each assembled upper starts with a BALIOS-lite stripper upper receiver. We then add our titanium gas block on the appropriate length barrel and finish the assembly with our BL-RAIL titanium barrel nut and our titanium T3 compensator. These uppers are perfect for those who are looking to do an SBR Pistol or suppressed 5.56mm build. Our full mass carrier is included as well as a BCM-Mod4 charging handle. - Barrel Material: 4150 Chrome Moly Vanadium - Twist Rate: 1:7 inches -  Finish: QPQ Nitride - Muzzle 1/2 x 28 thread - Carrier: Full mass QPQ Nitride body and gas key Stainless tail - Bolt: 9310 QPQ Nitride body and extractor Cryo'd MP tested - 7075 enhanced charging handle BCM-Mod 4 - Includes titanium T3 Comp - Weight: (2lbs 13.9oz M-Lok) (2Lbs 14.0oz KeyMod)]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H631]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[BARRELS]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[1087.78]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[1259]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[1399]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ALWBCGA]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006184]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A REGULATED BOLT CARRIER GROUP]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The Regulated Bolt Carrier (RBC) is a lightweight carrier with a gas regulating gate built into the carrier itself. This provides a drop in lightweight solution for those looking to tune your AR-15's gas system. It eliminates the need for adjustable gas blocks and allows the firearm to be restored to a factory full weight system by simply swapping your full-mass carrier back into your firearm. The RBC has infinite adjustment from fully open to fully closed on the regulating gate. The RBC can be tuned to most combinations of buffers springs suppressors and barrel lengths. The RBC Is fully adjustable through the port door and does not require the firearm to be broken down for adjustment -  Carrier: 8620 steel heat treated QPQ Nitride -  Bolt: 9310 steel heat treated MP Cryo'd QPQ Nitride - Rear body: 7075-T6 hard anodized clear - Extractor: machined heat treated QPQ Nitride - Carrier key: machined heat treated QPQ Nitride - Regulating gate: machined from 6AL-4V Titanium - Weight: 7.9oz assembled - Requires customer supplied T-6 Torx tool for adjustment]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[278.89]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[398]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[419]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2AMCRS2]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006009]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A BALIOS LITE BILLET UPPER & LOWER RCVR SET]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[With weight saving as the prime objective 2A-Armament set out to build a lightweight solution for those looking for a solid platform to build on. The BALIOS-lite has all the same great features and aesthetics as our standard BALIOS sets but incorporates a significant weight reduction. The BALIOS-lite is perfect for those who participate in 3-gun hunting or any other shooting activity where weight is a concern. Both the upper and lower receivers are equally at home on a standard forged product from other vendors. The flared magazine well aids in rapid reloading and the tapered transition under the charging handle prevents associated wear patterns from damaging the finish. We have eliminated the forward assist and retained the port door cover on the upper receiver. - 3-D Machined from U.S.A. Certified 7075-T6 plate aluminum - Machine textured magazine well compliments popular accessories - Pocketed design reduces weight and enhances appearance - Forward assist has been removed from upper to reduce weight - Bolt release features screw in pin (Included) - Integrated and lightened trigger guard - Upper receiver features M4 style feed ramps - Machined T-Markings and minimized logo for a clean appearance - Tapered charging handle ramp to eliminate unsightly wear marks - Integrated tensioning screw guaranties a tight fit (included) - Bead blasted and hard coat anodized black (Type3 class2) - Can be interchanged with forged or standard BALIOS sets - Weight: ( Lower 6.50 oz ) (Upper 5.85 oz ) Stripped - Product of the great state of Idaho MADE IN THE U.S.A.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H600]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[RIFLE]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[442]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[520]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ATICOMPT3]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006078]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A COMPENSATOR T3 TITANIUM BLASTED]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The T3 Titanium is a dual baffle compensator that directs expelled gasses to control muzzle direction. The initial baffle directs gas in a geometrical pattern that stabilizes the rifle system. The second baffle system channels gasses upward to compensate for muzzle rise. This gives the shooter the ability to decrease time between follow up shots and maintain control of muzzle direction. The T3 also mitigates some of the flash that is commonly associated with compensators when used on 16 and longer barrels. The T3 Titanium is made from 6AL-4V Titanium and represents a lightweight mounting solution for the GEMTECH GMT-HALO as well as the standard HALO suppressors. - 5.56mm/.223 caliber or smaller applications -  Machined on 8-axis Nakamura CNC machines - Made from U.S.A. Certified 6AL-4V Titanium - Bead blasted for a matte finish -  Threaded ﾽ x 28 TPI for common applications - Suppressor compatible (visit website list) - Length: 2.115 inches - Weight 1.35 oz - Product of Idaho MADE IN THE USA]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[88]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[125]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ATIGB1]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006085]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A GAS BLOCK .750 BORE ULTRA-LITE TITANIUM]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[53]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[75]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A 2ATITDP]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006108]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A TAKEDOWN PINS TITANIUM]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The 2A Armament Titanium takedown pin set features a through drilled design for maximum weight savings in a standard .250 pin size. The head of each pin also incorporates a pocketed feature to reduce weight. Each pin is machined with a single operation on our 8-Axis CNC Machines for true concentrically and consistency. Using certified U.S.A. 6AL-4V Titanium these pins weigh in at 0.18 oz total for both pins combined. The 2A Armament titanium takedown pins are aesthetically pleasing on both our BALIOS-lite receiver sets as well as other vendors product. - Mil-Spec .250 size - Made from U.S.A. Certified 6AL-4V titanium - Machined on 8-axis Nakamura CNC machines - Weight: 0.18 oz combined - Through drilled for weight reduction - Pocketed design - Bead blasted matte finish - Product of the great state of Idaho MADE IN THE U.S.A.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[26]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[38]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A CRF16PKM15BLK1]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006238]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A FACTORY 5.56 16 PENC BBL & 15 KEYMOD]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[Action: Semi Auto - Caliber: 5.56 - Finish: Black - Barrel Length: 16 - Weight: 5 lb - 2A-Armament has set out to deliver a factory built lightweight rifle that combines all of our most popular products into one high quality rifle. We start the foundation of our rifle with the popular BALIOS-lite receiver set. We then add in every titanium component we make and combine it with some of the best parts found throughout the industry to deliver a turn-key solution at a fair price. Key features include: our BL-RAIL that uses our tension lock design for attachment M-LOK or KeyMod mounting solution 6AL-4V titanium barrel nut titanium gas block titanium takedown pins and titanium T3 Compensator. These items add visual appeal as well as corrosion resistance. Each rifle is hand assembled when ordered test fired and backed by our great support staff. - LOWER RECEIVER: CNC machined 7075-T6 billet with flared mag-well hard coat type-III anodized rear tensioning screw rear takedown spring retainer screw in bolt catch pin. - UPPER RECEIVER: CNC machined 7075-T6 billet slick side mil-spec port door retained port door rod (No E-clip to lose!) M-4 feed ramps machined indexing marks. - BOLT AND CARRIER: 8620 machined body with QPQ process 9310 machined bolt cryogenically treated  MPT QPQ process BCM-mod4 charging handle. - BARREL: 16 Pencil profile 416-R stainless steel mid-length gas system 5.56 NATO spec chamber 1 in 8 twist 1/2x28 thread QPQ process titanium gas block. - RECEIVER EXTENSION: Mil-spec 6-position 7075-T6 standard H-Buffer. - HANDGUARD: 15 6061 extruded BL-RAIL M-LOK or KeyMod titanium barrel nut. - MUZZLE DEVICE: Titanium T3 compensator suppressor mount timed with steel shims. - STOCK/GRIP: MAGPUL MIAD Grip Mission First minimalist stock. - LOWER PARTS: Mil-spec safety magazine catch bolt catch through drilled titanium takedown pins. - TRIGGER: ALG-ACT trigger group with optional light or heavy hammer spring. - WEIGHT: 5 pounds based on options.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H600]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[RIFLE]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[1742]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[5]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[2177]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A CRF16PML15BLK1]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[854361006245]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A FACTORY 5.56 16 PENCIL BBL & 15 M-LOK]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[Action: Semi Auto - Caliber: 5.56 - Finish: Black - Stock: Magpul - Twist: 1:8 - Barrel Length: 16 - Weight: 5 lb - 2A-Armament has set out to deliver a factory built lightweight rifle that combines all of our most popular products into one high quality rifle. We start the foundation of our rifle with the popular BALIOS-lite receiver set. We then add in every titanium component we make and combine it with some of the best parts found throughout the industry to deliver a turn-key solution at a fair price. Key features include: our BL-RAIL that uses our tension lock design for attachment M-LOK or KeyMod mounting solution 6AL-4V titanium barrel nut titanium gas block titanium takedown pins and titanium T3 Compensator. These items add visual appeal as well as corrosion resistance. Each rifle is hand assembled when ordered test fired and backed by our great support staff. LOWER RECEIVER - CNC machined 7075-T6 billet with flared mag-well hard coat type-III anodized rear tensioning screw rear takedown spring retainer screw in bolt catch pin. UPPER RECEIVER - CNC machined 7075-T6 billet slick side mil-spec port door retained port door rod (No E-clip to lose!) M-4 feed ramps machined indexing marks. BOLT AND CARRIER - 8620 machined body with QPQ process 9310 machined bolt cryogenically treated  MPT QPQ process BCM-mod4 charging handle. BARREL - 16 Pencil profile 416-R stainless steel mid-length gas system 5.56 NATO spec chamber 1 in 8 twist 1/2x28 thread QPQ process titanium gas block. RECEIVER EXTENSION - Mil-spec 6-position 7075-T6 standard H-Buffer. HANDGUARD - 15 6061 extruded BL-RAIL M-LOK or KeyMod titanium barrel nut. MUZZLE DEVICE - Titanium T3 compensator suppressor mount timed with steel shims. STOCK/GRIP - MAGPUL MIAD Grip Mission First minimalist stock. LOWER PARTS - Mil-spec safety magazine catch bolt catch through drilled titanium takedown pins. TRIGGER - ALG-ACT trigger group with optional light or heavy hammer spring. WEIGHT - 5.0 pounds based on options. Ships with one MAGPUL P-MAG and die cut foam box.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H600]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[RIFLE]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[1742]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[2177]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A SHOWPAK1]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A SHOW DROP SHIP 1 ]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H600]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[RIFLE]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[4000]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[25]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[4800]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[2A SHOWPAK2]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[2A SHOW DROP SHIP 2 ]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H600]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[RIFLE]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[6600]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[35]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[8250]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100114]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002619]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC MUZZLE BRAKE 50BMG 80T 1-14]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The AAC Blackout is a highly-efficient muzzle brake design and compatible with AAC sound suppressors. Both the 338 Titan-QD and the 50 BMG Cyclops muzzle brakes are precision machined from aerospace-grade heat-treated 17-4 stainless steel and SCARmor coated for high surface hardness and durability.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[267.56]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.8]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[398.99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100115]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002626]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC MUZZLE BRAKE 50BMG 80T 7/8-14]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The AAC Blackout is a highly-efficient muzzle brake design and compatible with AAC sound suppressors. Both the 338 Titan-QD and the 50 BMG Cyclops muzzle brakes are precision machined from aerospace-grade heat-treated 17-4 stainless steel and SCARmor coated for high surface hardness and durability.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[267.56]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.82]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[398.99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100183]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002749]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC MUZZLE BRAKE 5.56MM 51T 1/2-28]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[This AAC Blackout AR-15 Muzzle Brake is a highly efficient and effective brake designed to significantly reduce recoil and help keep shooters on target for faster shot-to-shot recovery. All Blackout muzzle brakes are machined from high strength aerospace 17-4 stainless steel alloy and coated in a hard durable corrosion resistant SCARmor finish. This 51T Blackout muzzle brake works in conjunction with AAC's improved ratchet mount sound suppressors. The 51-T mount is an intuitive lightning fast silencer attachment/detachment system that allows for secure installation of a suppressor in less than 3 seconds with no tools or moving parts. Not compatible with the older spring mount (18-Tooth) or newer ratchet taper mount (90-Tooth) sound suppressors Caliber: 22 Cal/5.56mm - Thread Pitch: 1/2-28 - Common Firearm Use: AR-15 Bushmaster ACR - Finish: SCARmor - Silencer Mount: 51T Ratchet Mount - AAC Silencer Compatibility: ACR-SD 416-SD 249-SD Post-2007 M4-2000 Mini 4 Post-Mid 2010 7.62-SD 7.62-SDN6 Mini 7]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[100.59]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.3]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[149.99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100184]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002695]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC MUZZLE BRAKE MK13-SD 7.62MM 90T 5/8-24]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The AAC Blackout Muzzle Brake is a highly efficient and effective brake designed to significantly reduce recoil and help keep shooters on target for faster shot-to-shot recovery. All Blackout muzzle brakes are machined from high strength aerospace 17-4 stainless steel alloy and coated in a hard durable corrosion resistant SCARmor finish. This 90-Tooth Blackout muzzle brake works in conjunction with AAC's Non-Tapering Ratchet Mount designed specifically for use with the MK13-SD Silencer. The new 90T gear on the brake interfaces with a spring biased ratchet lever on the suppressor to eliminate the potential for the silencer to inadvertently unthread during firing while a finer pitch external ACME thread snugs it up securely to create a rock solid platform. Caliber: 30 Cal/7.62mm - Thread Pitch: 5/8-24 - Common Firearm Use: Bolt Action 7.62mm or 300 Win Mag M2010 - Length: 2.25 - Weight: 2.4 oz - Finish: SCARmor - Silencer Mount: 90-T Ratchet Mount - AAC Silencer Compatibility: MK13-SD - NOTE: This brake is designed specifically for use with AAC's MK13-SD Silencers and is NOT compatible with other 90-Tooth Silencers such as the SR5 or SR7.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[114]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.25]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[169.99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100186]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002114]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC BRAKEOUT COMPENSATOR 5.56MM 51T 1/2-28]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[The AAC Brakeout Flash Hider Muzzle Brake combines the best features of AAC's Blackout flash hiders and Blackout muzzle brakes into a single high performing unit. The Breakout's rear muzzle brake chamber is open on both sides and on the top for reduced perceived recoil & muzzle rise yet closed on the bottom for minimal environmental disturbance when shooting from the bench or prone positions. The 3-prong front end incorporates elements of the Blackout flash hider's effective design to minimize muzzle flash. All Breakout flash hider muzzle brakes are machined from high strength aerospace 17-4 stainless steel alloy and coated in a hard durable corrosion resistant SCARmor finish. This 51T Brakeout works in conjunction with AAC's improved ratchet mount sound suppressors. The 51-T mount is an intuitive lightning fast silencer attachment/detachment system that allows for secure installation of a suppressor in less than 3 seconds with no tools or moving parts. Not compatible with the older spring mount (18-Tooth) or newer ratchet taper mount (90-Tooth) sound suppressors. Caliber: 22 Cal/5.56mm - Thread Pitch: 1/2-28 - Finish: SCARmor - Silencer Mount: 51T Ratchet Mount - AAC Silencer Compatibility: ACR-SD 416-SD 249-SD Post-2007 M4-2000 Mini 4 Post-Mid 2010 7.62-SD 7.62-SDN6 Mini 7 - NOTE: Muzzle Brake Barrel Shims are enclosed Inside the Factory Instructional Insert.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[62.7]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.34]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100206]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002275]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC 51T B/O FLASH HIDER 5.56MM 1/2-28]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[This AAC Blackout AR-15 Flash Hider is an extremely efficient design that effectively eliminates muzzle flash even on short barrels. The open-end 3-prong design of the Blackout is inherently stronger than 4-prong units and is not subject to the wear and erosion commonly encountered with closed-end designs. All Blackout flash suppressors are machined from high strength aerospace steel alloy and coated in a hard durable corrosion resistant SCARmor finish. This 51T Blackout flash hider works in conjunction with AAC's improved ratchet mount sound suppressors. The 51-T mount is an intuitive lightning fast silencer attachment/detachment system that allows for secure installation of a suppressor in less than 3 seconds with no tools or moving parts. Not compatible with the older spring mount (18-Tooth) or newer ratchet taper mount (90-Tooth) sound suppressors. Caliber: 22 Cal/5.56mm - Thread Pitch: 1/2-28 - Common Firearm Use: AR-15 Bushmaster ACR - Length: 2.5 - Length Added to Barrel: 1.875 - Weight: 4.3 oz - Finish: SCARmor - Silencer Mount: 51T Ratchet Mount - AAC Silencer Compatibility: ACR-SD 416-SD 249-SD Post-2007 M4-2000 Mini 4 Post-Mid 2010 7.62-SD 7.62-SDN6 Mini 7]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[66.39]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.33]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[98.99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100214]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002336]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC 51T B/O FLASH HIDER 7.62MM .595-32 M14 & M1A]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[This AAC Blackout Flash Hider is an extremely efficient design that effectively eliminates muzzle flash even on short barrels. The open-end 3-prong design of the Blackout is inherently stronger than 4-prong units and is not subject to the wear and erosion commonly encountered with closed-end designs. All Blackout flash suppressors are machined from high strength aerospace steel alloy and coated in a hard durable corrosion resistant SCARmor finish. This 51T Blackout flash hider works in conjunction with AAC's improved ratchet mount sound suppressors. The 51-T mount is an intuitive lightning fast silencer attachment/detachment system that allows for secure installation of a suppressor in less than 3 seconds with no tools or moving parts. Not compatible with the older spring mount (18-Tooth) or newer ratchet taper mount (90-Tooth) sound suppressors. Caliber: 30 Cal/7.62mm (Also 6.8 and 6.5mm) - Thread Pitch: .595-32 - Common Firearm Use: M14 Springfield M1A - Length: 2.5 - Length Added to Barrel: 1.875 - Weight: 4.35 oz - Finish: SCARmor - Silencer Mount: 51T Ratchet Mount - AAC Silencer Compatibility: 6.8 SPC M4-2000 Post-Mid 2010 7.62-SD 7.62-SDN6 Mini 7]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H660]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[HUNTING ACCESSORIES]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[62.7]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[0.3]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[99]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100392]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[847128000310]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC SILENCER CYCLONE 7.62MM 5/8-24 DIRECT THR]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[Caliber: 7.62mm - TPI: 5/8-24 - The rigidly simple threaded mounting design provides reliable precision accuracy with minimal and repeatable zero-shift. Extraordinary sound and recoil reduction are two of the instant benefits of the CYCLONE silencer. Durability is maximized by fully CNC automated fusion welding of every high-temperature aerospace alloy component used in its construction- making 100% suppressed fire possible. The back-pressure lowering design of the silencer aids in shooter comfort reduces weapon fouling and minimizes cyclic rate increase. EDM technology is utilized as a final step to ensure precise bore alignment and enhance accuracy. The elimination of approximately 95% of the muzzle report nullifies the need for ear protection facilitates field communications and masks the location of the user.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H606]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[SILENCERS - SOT ITEM]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[452]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[1.25]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[695.95]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100398]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[847128000266]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC SILENCER M4-2000 51T 5.56MM RIFLE]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[Caliber: 5.56 NATO - Sound Reduction: 32-34dB - Mount: 51T Ratchet Mount - Materials: Inconel 718 & 316L SS - Finish: Cerakote - Length: 6.625 - Length Added: 5.10 - Diameter: 1.50 - Weight: 7.6 oz - The worlds most effective 5.56mm silencer just got better. AAC's M4-2000 Mod 08 features the patent pending fast-attach Ratchet-Mount to provide precision accuracy with minimal and repeatable zero-shift. Users have the ability to install or remove the silencer from the Blackout flash hider/muzzle brake or the BRAKEOUT compensator in seconds. The compact size and light weight have minimal affect on maneuverability. The M4-2000 Mod 08s extreme durability is maximized by CNC automated fusion welding of every high-temperature aerospace alloy component used in its construction- making 100% suppressed full-auto fire possible on barrels as short as 10 inches. The back-pressure lowering design of the silencer aids in shooter comfort reduces weapon fouling and minimizes cyclic rate increase. As a final step tapered-bore EDM technology is utilized to ensure precise bore alignment resulting in enhanced accuracy and maximum performance. By eliminating approximately 97% of the muzzle report the M4-2000 Mod 08 preserves the hearing of the shooter and nearby support personnel. Eliminating muzzle flash in the harshest of environments. - This silencer installs to your rifle with one of the following muzzle devices: - BRAKEOUT 51T Compensator - BLACKOUT 51T Flash Hider - BLACKOUT 51T Muzzle Brake]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H606]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[SILENCERS - SOT ITEM]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[482]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[1.1]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[795]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100410]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[847128000143]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC SILENCER CYCLOPS 50CAL 80T RIFLE]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[Caliber: .50 BMG - Sound Reduction: 32dB - Mount: 50BMG Ratchet - Materials: Alloy Steel - Finish: SCARmor - Length: 15.75 - Length Added: 12.65 - Diameter: 2.50 - Weight: 4 lbs 15 oz - The CYCLOPS is a compact light-weight sound and flash suppressor designed to reduce the sound and visible flash signature of bolt action and single shot rifles chambering the .50 BMG cartridge. The revolutionary design of the CYCLOPS significantly reduces felt recoil environmental disturbance and preserves the hearing of shooters and observers by delivering an overall sound signature well below the pain threshold and risk limit for hearing loss. The CYCLOPS is constructed of specially heat treated high strength alloys and is CNC fusion welded to yield a structure that can withstand the intense pressures of the .50 BMG cartridge. The CYCLOPS couples to a proprietary muzzle brake using a durable ACME type thread and a spring biased secondary latch allowing users to install or remove the suppressor in less than 10 seconds. Both the suppressor and muzzle brake are finished in Matte Black.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H606]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[SILENCERS - SOT ITEM]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[1678]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[4.9]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[2595.95]]></msrp>
	</node>
	<node>
		<product_name><![CDATA[AAC 100420]]></product_name>
		<universal_product_code><![CDATA[857839002978]]></universal_product_code>
		<short_description><![CDATA[AAC SILENCER TI-RANT 45ACP .578-28]]></short_description>
		<long_description><![CDATA[Caliber: .45 ACP - Sound Reduction: 30dB Dry / 41dB Wet - Mount: ASAP Piston System - Materials: Grade 9 Ti 17-4PH 7075-T6 - Finish: Cerakote - Length: 8.74 - Diameter: 1.38 - Weight: 11.5 oz - The Ti-RANT .45 is the worldﾒs first silencer for .45 ACP pistols that is truly stealthy when fired dry. The average dry sound signature of the Ti-RANT .45 is 133 dB when fired on a Heckler and Koch USP Tactical .45 with Remington 230 grain ammunition. This puts the dry performance of the Ti-RANT .45 squarely in the ballpark of most competitor's 9mm pistol silencers. With a wet charge of 5ccﾒs of water the sound signature drops to 125 dB. To put it another way our .45 silencer is quieter than some companyﾒs .22 silencers. The Ti-RANT .45 does not stand out among a sea of posers just because of its jaw-dropping performance. Intelligent material selection gives the Ti-RANT .45 unequalled durability in a deceptively light-weight package. The Ti-RANT .45 incorporates AACﾒs new A.S.A.P. CLUTCH. This highly evolved Nielsen device enables flawless semi-automatic operation on all relevant host pistols and can be fully disassembled for cleaning or piston replacement with no tools in seconds. The Ti-RANT .45 can be outfitted with pistons threaded M16 x 1 Right Hand M16 x 1 Left Hand and two pistons threaded .578-28; one extended for the Sig P-220 and 1911ﾒs with a full length guide rod and a flush mount for 1911ﾒs with a standard G.I. guide rod. For multi-caliber use pistons are available in the most common 9mm and .40 thread patterns to allow use of the Ti-RANT 45 on hosts in those calibers.]]></long_description>
		<category_code><![CDATA[H606]]></category_code>
		<category_description><![CDATA[SILENCERS - SOT ITEM]]></category_description>
		<product_price><![CDATA[482]]></product_price>
		<small_image_path><![CDATA[]]></small_image_path>
		<large_image_path><![CDATA[]]></large_image_path>
		<product_weight><![CDATA[2]]></product_weight>
		<marp><![CDATA[]]></marp>
		<msrp><![CDATA[809]]></msrp>
	</node>
</data>
